This is Trigun.
guitar solo
.
Oh, my God.
Vash.
Vash!
Come on, Vash.
Stand up already.
Let's go!
Hey!
Don't be that way.
It's just you and me here.
We should at least try
to act like brothers.
Murderer!
Your whole life is a lie!
You killed Rem! The crew!
You killed them all!
Yeah.
Spectacular, huh?
They all die. Except,
of course, for the fraction who will
survive because of Rem's incessant meddling.
Where are you going?
There's no use staying here. Come on.
Or would you rather just lay there
and cry your little eyes out?
This is a terrible environment,
just as I predicted it would be.
It'll be impossible for
any garbage to live here.
It can still work out
if they have the plans.
Yeah, probably.
They'll survive by leeching
off the blood of our siblings,
gorging themselves like parasites.
I can hear the screams
of our brethren now,
the anguished death cries of our friends.
Is that why you kill people?
That's right.
I kill spiders to save the butterflies.
It's simple logic.
Don't forget.
He killed them. That's right.
He killed...
Rem, help!
No one ever has the right
to take the life of another.
Come on, hurry up, let's get going!
That is the true nature of these
pathetic beasts known as humans.
They're all selfish, arrogant,
insolent, grossly imperfect organisms.
They make me sick to my stomach.
what is that what did
you do what are you doing
when you and i were born
we had free will we're
no longer merely things
to be used by humans
what is he saying
I found it damage isn't all that
bad it's usable what are you
planning to do with this I have to
go after something I left behind I'm
going to look for this might take a
little while I suggest to stay here
but nice it's
hard to be alone I
don't want to be alone someone nice
all done nice hey now where are you going
only a 13 % output that's the
best we can get what is that these
are new siblings and this one will
be yours we will use these guns
to dispose of mankind I'm not
gonna do that yes you will never
then why did you follow me and wait
until I returned because you're
hopeless on your own isn't that
right very well watch me then
don't
after
years are you still
so affected by that ridiculous
nonsense that fantasy world created
for you by the woman who lived
and died by contradiction I won't
let Don't you kill any more people!
Sorry, dear brother.
I think you misunderstood me.
You're aiming at the wrong person.
They're still alive. Alive!
I promised Rim that we would make
this land... Exactly. We will.
You and I will make this
land into our very own Eden.
Just for us.
It's wrong.
This is wrong.
It's wrong!
My leg...
My leg, it hurts. Why?
Why?
There's so much pain in my leg!
Did you shoot me?
Did you actually shoot me?
I can't believe this!
Did you really shoot me?
No! Wait!
Fast!
Rem...
Where am I?
This man is related to Rem.
He's still alive.
I have to tell him about Rem.
Hey there, Bash.
Now everything that joined you
and Rem together is finally gone.
Is that your excuse for killing?
Haven't you learned anything
over the past hundred years?
The scars they carved into your
body will never regenerate.
Symbolic of your foolish waste
of energy on this human garbage.
Regardless of how you feel about
them, they are living beings.
They deserve to live!
What's the use of growing
up if the only thing
that grows is your useless sentimentalism?
You're still a
good-for-nothing pathetic whip!
What the hell is that?
This is our gift, brother.
Now it's time to take out this
worthless human garbage forever!
Are you going to shoot me again?
Are you actually gonna shoot me again?
Make Vess suffer.
Make him suffer for all eternity.
I will, my master.
I promise the man belonging
to this arm will suffer.
Now's the end of Vash the Stampede!
You and this town die together!
You're naive.
Had I been so inclined,
I could have killed you at
least three times by then.
Did you kill them or not?
Damn, you are a noisy one, aren't you?
What if I did, chicken shit?
Come on.
I mean, you're dead.
Ready?
Run!
What is that?
I don't understand!
What the hell is that thing?
It should never end this way.
What other alternative do I
have if we're going to survive?
All lives are too different, Vash.
And he's not alone.
I failed.
I failed to save someone again.
Just be more careful the next time.
Come on, it's time to choose.
You have free will.
The humans treat you well?
Did you have fun, dear brother?
I did, yeah.
Best thing that ever happened to me.
I don't know.
Uh-oh!
Damn it!
Ugh!
Oh, my God.
Huh?
Hmph!
He cancelled me out.
I didn't create these weapons
to be wasted like that.
Using them this way is the only thing
that gives them any meaning at all.
It's hopeless isn't it
I've made my decision
You're not a human being you're a plant I
know that you're a
superior being I disagree
You're wrong about this Bash I
won't make the same mistake twice
You can't hold me here!
Oh, my God.
What are you doing, Tito Noggin?
It's right next to you!
Use it, David!
You're way! Oh! Ah!
però! Jiet!
Uh...
Yeah!
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
I, I will survive.
Water!
Weakest water! Yeah.
Vash will come back. Won't you?
Of course you will.
You wouldn't dare keep a
good woman like me waiting.
Right?
Right.
Ram, I will continue to believe in you,
but from now on, I'll look
to my own words for Guidance.
The sky under the sky,
the wind is in the future.
The day of the day of the
sky, the light of the sky,
the light
of the
sky?
I'll leave you in the next video.